{
   
  "gh1912": {
    "subject": "Test your Spanish translation skills",
    "help": "Choose the word that is the best translation for the displayed word",
    "data": [
    {
        "questionType": "translate",
        "question": "comida",
        "answers": ["food", "eating", "to share", "sister"],
        "correctAnswer": "food"
      },
    {
        "questionType": "translate",
        "question": "perro",
        "answers": ["dog", "father", "angry", "pet"],
        "correctAnswer": "dog"
      },
    {
        "questionType": "translate",
        "question": "hermano",
        "answers": ["brother", "father", "sister", "crab"],
        "correctAnswer": "brother"
      },
    {
        "questionType": "translate",
        "question": "escribir",
        "answers": ["to write", "to read", "to scribble", "money"],
        "correctAnswer": "to write"
      },
    {
        "questionType": "translate",
        "question": "dinero",
        "answers": ["money", "dinner", "to cook", "mother"],
        "correctAnswer": "money"
      },
    {
        "questionType": "translate",
        "question": "borrador",
        "answers": ["eraser", "border", "dog", "teacher"],
        "correctAnswer": "eraser"
      },
     {
        "questionType": "translate",
        "question": "nadar",
        "answers": ["to swim", "sister", "friend", "eraser"],
        "correctAnswer": "to swim"
      },
    {
        "questionType": "translate",
        "question": "casa",
        "answers": ["house", "to marry", "food", "teacher"],
        "correctAnswer": "house"
      },
    {
        "questionType": "translate",
        "question": "camisa",
        "answers": ["shirt", "skirt", "to write", "money"],
        "correctAnswer": "shirt"
      },
    {
        "questionType": "translate",
        "question": "pez",
        "answers": ["fish", "candy", "angry", "cat"],
        "correctAnswer": "fish"
      }
    ]
  }
  
}